[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The redunknown cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"What is the material of the medium cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Dirt"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Wood"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium brick cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Is the medium brick cube heavier than the medium dirt cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium dirt cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has larger restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium brick cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium dirt cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium dirt cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium brick cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium dirt cube travel to quadrant \u2162?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium brick cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium dirt cube collide with the large RedUnknown cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium dirt cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large redunknown cube and the medium brick cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The wall and the medium dirt cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium brick cube and the medium dirt cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The wall and the medium brick cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium dirt cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The wall and the large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium dirt cube and the large redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium dirt cube and the medium brick cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the large RedUnknown cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]